[
            {
                "question": ": &nbsp How can you open a link in a new browser window?",
                "choice1": "< a href='url' new>",
                "choice2": "< a href='url' target='new'>",
                "choice3": "< a href='url' target='_blank'>",
                "choice4": "< a href='url' target=''>",
                "answer": 3
            },
            
            {
                "question": ": &nbsp How many rings are on the Olympic flag?",
                "choice1": "4",
                "choice2": "5",
                "choice3": "7",
                "choice4": "none",
                "answer": 2
            },

            {
                "question": ": &nbsp  Which of these animals does NOT appear in the Chinese zodiac?",
                "choice1": "Bear ",
                "choice2": "Rabbit",
                "choice3": "Dragon",
                "choice4": "Dog",
                "answer": 1
            },
            {
                "question": ": &nbsp  What does CSS stand for?",
                "choice1": "Cascading Style Sheet ",
                "choice2": "Creative Style Sheets",
                "choice3": "Colorful Style Sheets",
                "choice4": "Computer Style Sheets",
                "answer": 1
            },
            {
                "question": ": &nbsp How can you created rounded corners using CSS3?",
                "choice1": "border[round]: 30px;",
                "choice2": "corner-effect: round;",
                "choice3": "border-radius: 30px;",
                "choice4": "alpha-effect: round-corner;",
                "answer": 3
            },
            {
                "question": ": &nbsp How do you add shadow to elements in CSS3?",
                "choice1": "shadow-right: 10px shadow-bottom: 10px;",
                "choice2": "box-shadow: 10px 10px 5px grey;",
                "choice3": "shadow-color: grey;",
                "choice4": "alpha-effect[shadow]: 10px 10px 5px grey;",
                "answer": 2
            },
            {
                "question": ": &nbsp B2CD,  _____ BCD4, B5CD, BC6D",
                "choice1": "B2C2D",
                "choice2": "BC3D",
                "choice3": "B2C3D",
                "choice4": "BCD7",
                "answer": 2
            },
            {
                "question": ": &nbsp Here are some words translated from an artificial language.<br>slar means jump<br>slary means jumping<br>slarend means jumped<br>Which word could mean 'playing'”?",
                "choice1": "B2C2D",
                "choice2": "BC3D",
                "choice3": "B2C3D",
                "choice4": "BCD7",
                "answer": 2
            },
            {
                "question": ": &nbsp PEDAL : BICYCLE",
                "choice1": "inch : yardstick",
                "choice2": "walk : skip",
                "choice3": "tire : automobile",
                "choice4": "buckle : belt",
                "answer": 4
            },
            {
                "question": ": &nbsp What is the name of this symbol: ¶",
                "choice1": "Fermata",
                "choice2": "Pilcrow ",
                "choice3": "Interrobang",
                "choice4": "Biltong",
                "answer": 2
            }

        ]
